PhotoReqID,Category,PhotoName,PhotoDescription
OC1,Overall Compound,Overall Compound 1,Photo of site walk document / folder with site ID (This should always be your first photo)
OC2,Overall Compound,Overall Compound 2,Compound from ground level (ALL sides & surrounding area)
OC3,Overall Compound,Overall Compound 3,At least (1) photo of overall tower (Photos facing each subject carrier sector preferred)
OC4,Overall Compound,Overall Compound 4,"Zoom in on each antenna sector for subject carrier ONLY (Straight on & from each side of antenna mount, all sectors)"
OC5,Overall Compound,Overall Compound 5,"Site signage (Site number, FCC number - Warning signage is not needed)"
OC6,Overall Compound,Overall Compound 6,Stand inside corners of compound - Take (3) pics: Looking down fence line (both directions) & middle of compound
UD1,Utility Demarcs,Utility Demarcs 1,All shared utility h-frames inside/outside compound ( All sides & close-ups of equipment attached)
UD2,Utility Demarcs,Utility Demarcs 2,"Fiber Demarc/Meet-me-point (Illustrate on site sketch, obtain coordinates; Detailed & overall pictures) (If applicable)"
UD3,Utility Demarcs,Utility Demarcs 3,Fiber demarc coordinates & brief description of type/location:
UD4,Utility Demarcs,Utility Demarcs 4,"Transformer including information tag (nameplate) and rating (Pad, vault, or pole mounted)"
UD5,Utility Demarcs,Utility Demarcs 5,Power lines/conduits running from transformer to site (If possible/applicable)
UD6,Utility Demarcs,Utility Demarcs 6,Meter w/ label & Photo of Disconnect Breaker or fuse rating (Should be next to meter w/ size indicated on breaker switch)
SCLA1,Subject Carrier Lease Area,Subject Carrier Lease Area 1,Overall platform/pad/shelter view (Should provide a general view of all equipment)
SCLA2,Subject Carrier Lease Area,Subject Carrier Lease Area 2,Profile view of all (4) sides of equipment platform/pad/shelter (Should be as clear and unobstructed as possible)
SCLA3,Subject Carrier Lease Area,Subject Carrier Lease Area 3,Carrier H-frame (Views from ALL sides and close-up views of equipment that is attached) (When present)
SCLA4,Subject Carrier Lease Area,Subject Carrier Lease Area 4,Carrier Telco: Telco board/Ciena/AAV & related junctions boxes (May vary by site. Can be inside shelter/on h-frame)
SCLA5,Subject Carrier Lease Area,Subject Carrier Lease Area 5,Ice Bridge/Cable Trays/Conduit Runs to tower from subject carrier equipment (Capture labels printed on cables)
SCLA6,Subject Carrier Lease Area,Subject Carrier Lease Area 6,"Ice Bridge posts (Show where they’re located on pad/platform, if applicable) Put distance between posts on sketch"
SCLA7,Subject Carrier Lease Area,Subject Carrier Lease Area 7,Radios/System Modules (Multiple views so mounts/grounding/cabling is visible)
SCLA8,Subject Carrier Lease Area,Subject Carrier Lease Area 8,Photograph space(s) within subject carrier lease area where equipment will fit (When SOW is adding equipment)
SCLA9,Subject Carrier Lease Area,Subject Carrier Lease Area 9,"All cabinets on pads/platforms/shelters (Get overall photo, zoomed in photos of ALL internals including make/model, BBUs, rack mounted equipment, etc.)
 PLEASE GET INSIDES OF CABINETS & CAPTURE RECTIFIERS/CONVERTERS/BREAKERS/EMPTY SLOTS/BATTERIES…etc."
EL1,Electrical,Electrical 1,"Any and all ground bars associated with subject carrier (At Radios, at tower, under ice bridge, on h-frame, in shelter, etc.)"
EL2,Electrical,Electrical 2,"Inside of DC Power Plant: Converters, rectifiers, batteries, empty slots, digital ready outs, power distribution units (PDU), other equipment."
EL3,Electrical,Electrical 3,Manufacturer sticker on multi-meter gang bank/trough. Usually indicates the incoming service on site; very important. (if not a stand alone meter)
EL4,Electrical,Electrical 4,Shelter sites: HVAC nameplate/sticker for subject carrier only. Other carrier's HVAC info not needed.
AEL1,Additional Electrical,Additional Electrical 1,Meter Bank with labeling and carrier/tenant name (Close up of existing tenant meter- meter number visible)
AEL2,Additional Electrical,Additional Electrical 2,"Manual Disconnect(s): Overall view, and nameplate photo of voltage/amperage/make"
AEL3,Additional Electrical,Additional Electrical 3,Automatic Transfer Switch (ATS)/Manual Transfer Switch (MTS may be within integrated PPC)
AEL4,Additional Electrical,Additional Electrical 4,Existing PPC (Breaker Panel) (Be sure to get inside: Clear photos of panel schedule/breaker sizes/empty slots/labeling)
AEL5,Additional Electrical,Additional Electrical 5,PPC generator plug/stand-alone gen plug (If present)
AEL6,Additional Electrical,Additional Electrical 6,Generator: Overall and zoomed in
AEL7,Additional Electrical,Additional Electrical 7,Generator name plate and detailed photos (If applicable) (Be sure to get voltage/phase/kW rating)
OC1LA1,Other Carrier's Existing Lease Areas #1,Other Carrier's Existing Lease Areas #1_1,Overall view of each carrier’s lease space (Provide multiple images to aid in perspective if possible)
OC1LA2,Other Carrier's Existing Lease Areas #1,Other Carrier's Existing Lease Areas #1_2,"Four photos of equipment pad – one from each side (Make sure all cabinets are visible, no need to zoom on them)"
OC1LA3,Other Carrier's Existing Lease Areas #1,Other Carrier's Existing Lease Areas #1_3,H-frame(s) (Overall photos for location reference) (If applicable)
OC1LA4,Other Carrier's Existing Lease Areas #1,Other Carrier's Existing Lease Areas #1_4,AAV equipment: Cienas/AAV/telco cabs
OC1LA5,Other Carrier's Existing Lease Areas #1,Other Carrier's Existing Lease Areas #1_5,Junction box(es)
OC1LA6,Other Carrier's Existing Lease Areas #1,Other Carrier's Existing Lease Areas #1_6,Ice Bridge/cable tray/ladder (Overall photos showing their locations)
OC1LA7,Other Carrier's Existing Lease Areas #1,Other Carrier's Existing Lease Areas #1_7,"Ice Bridge posts (Showing where they’re located within compound, if applicable & especially if close to lease area)"
OC1LA8,Other Carrier's Existing Lease Areas #1,Other Carrier's Existing Lease Areas #1_8,Meter Bank with labeling and carrier/tenant name
OC1LA9,Other Carrier's Existing Lease Areas #1,Other Carrier's Existing Lease Areas #1_9,Manual Disconnect(s)
OC1LA10,Other Carrier's Existing Lease Areas #1,Other Carrier's Existing Lease Areas #1_10,Automatic Transfer Switch (ATS)/Manual Transfer Switch (MTS may be within integrated PPC)
OC1LA11,Other Carrier's Existing Lease Areas #1,Other Carrier's Existing Lease Areas #1_11,PPC (Breaker Panel) exterior
OC2LA1,Other Carrier's Existing Lease Areas #2,Other Carrier's Existing Lease Areas #2_1,Overall view of each carrier’s lease space (Provide multiple images to aid in perspective if possible)
OC2LA2,Other Carrier's Existing Lease Areas #2,Other Carrier's Existing Lease Areas #2_2,"Four photos of equipment pad – one from each side (Make sure all cabinets are visible, no need to zoom on them)"
OC2LA3,Other Carrier's Existing Lease Areas #2,Other Carrier's Existing Lease Areas #2_3,H-frame(s) (Overall photos for location reference) (If applicable)
OC2LA4,Other Carrier's Existing Lease Areas #2,Other Carrier's Existing Lease Areas #2_4,AAV equipment: Cienas/AAV/telco cabs
OC2LA5,Other Carrier's Existing Lease Areas #2,Other Carrier's Existing Lease Areas #2_5,Junction box(es)
OC2LA6,Other Carrier's Existing Lease Areas #2,Other Carrier's Existing Lease Areas #2_6,Ice Bridge/cable tray/ladder (Overall photos showing their locations)
OC2LA7,Other Carrier's Existing Lease Areas #2,Other Carrier's Existing Lease Areas #2_7,"Ice Bridge posts (Showing where they’re located within compound, if applicable & especially if close to lease area)"
OC2LA8,Other Carrier's Existing Lease Areas #2,Other Carrier's Existing Lease Areas #2_8,Meter Bank with labeling and carrier/tenant name
OC2LA9,Other Carrier's Existing Lease Areas #2,Other Carrier's Existing Lease Areas #2_9,Manual Disconnect(s)
OC2LA10,Other Carrier's Existing Lease Areas #2,Other Carrier's Existing Lease Areas #2_10,Automatic Transfer Switch (ATS)/Manual Transfer Switch (MTS may be within integrated PPC)
OC2LA11,Other Carrier's Existing Lease Areas #2,Other Carrier's Existing Lease Areas #2_11,PPC (Breaker Panel) exterior
OC3LA1,Other Carrier's Existing Lease Areas #3,Other Carrier's Existing Lease Areas #3_1,Overall view of each carrier’s lease space (Provide multiple images to aid in perspective if possible)
OC3LA2,Other Carrier's Existing Lease Areas #3,Other Carrier's Existing Lease Areas #3_2,"Four photos of equipment pad – one from each side (Make sure all cabinets are visible, no need to zoom on them)"
OC3LA3,Other Carrier's Existing Lease Areas #3,Other Carrier's Existing Lease Areas #3_3,H-frame(s) (Overall photos for location reference) (If applicable)
OC3LA4,Other Carrier's Existing Lease Areas #3,Other Carrier's Existing Lease Areas #3_4,AAV equipment: Cienas/AAV/telco cabs
OC3LA5,Other Carrier's Existing Lease Areas #3,Other Carrier's Existing Lease Areas #3_5,Junction box(es)
OC3LA6,Other Carrier's Existing Lease Areas #3,Other Carrier's Existing Lease Areas #3_6,Ice Bridge/cable tray/ladder (Overall photos showing their locations)
OC3LA7,Other Carrier's Existing Lease Areas #3,Other Carrier's Existing Lease Areas #3_7,"Ice Bridge posts (Showing where they’re located within compound, if applicable & especially if close to lease area)"
OC3LA8,Other Carrier's Existing Lease Areas #3,Other Carrier's Existing Lease Areas #3_8,Meter Bank with labeling and carrier/tenant name
OC3LA9,Other Carrier's Existing Lease Areas #3,Other Carrier's Existing Lease Areas #3_9,Manual Disconnect(s)
OC3LA10,Other Carrier's Existing Lease Areas #3,Other Carrier's Existing Lease Areas #3_10,Automatic Transfer Switch (ATS)/Manual Transfer Switch (MTS may be within integrated PPC)
OC3LA11,Other Carrier's Existing Lease Areas #3,Other Carrier's Existing Lease Areas #3_11,PPC (Breaker Panel) exterior
TD1,Tower Details,Tower Details,"ALL Antennas and ancillary equipment on Tower (Overall tower, zoomed in photos of each sector of subject carrier)"
SS1,Self-Support,Self-Support 1,Subject Carrier Cable Ladder location on Tower
SS2,Self-Support,Self-Support 2,Safety Climb location
SS3,Self-Support,Self-Support 3,"Tower foundation(s) - Overall, close-up"
SS4,Self-Support,Self-Support 4,Tower Foundation Diameter(s) or Size (Provide on sketch or as-built markup) :
SS5,Self-Support,Self-Support 5,Tower Face width (Provide on sketch or as-built markup) :
MP1,Monopole,Monopole 1,Take photos of open coax ports (Bottom of Tower)
MP2,Monopole,Monopole 2,Space inside Monopole for multiple coax? Space inside Monopole for (1-2) hybrid cables?
MP3,Monopole,Monopole 3,Safety Climb location
MP4,Monopole,Monopole 4,"Tower foundation - Overall, close-up"
MP5,Monopole,Monopole 5,Tower Foundation Diameter or Size (Provide on sketch or as-built markup) :
MP6,Monopole,Monopole 6,Tower Diameter (Provide on sketch or as-built markup) :
GD1,Guyed Tower,Guyed Tower 1,Subject Carrier Cable Location on Tower
GD2,Guyed Tower,Guyed Tower 2,Safety Climb Location
GD3,Guyed Tower,Guyed Tower 3,Tower Foundation Diameter or Size (Provide on sketch or as-built markup) :
GD4,Guyed Tower,Guyed Tower 4,Tower Face width (Provide on sketch or as-built markup) :
GD5,Guyed Tower,Guyed Tower 5,Zoom to guy anchor points on tower if near to Subject Carrier RAD Center/mounts
